{
    "subject": "resource/Boles\u0142aw_Wallek-Walewski",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Lviv",
    "human_readable": "Boles\u0142aw Wallek-Walewski was born in Lviv.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9503310322761536,
            "question": "Where was Boles\u0142aw Wallek-Walewski born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9495977759361267,
            "question": "Were there any significant events happening in Lviv during Boles\u0142aw Wallek-Walewski's birth year?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7581973075866699,
            "question": "What is Boles\u0142aw Wallek-Walewski known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6809021234512329,
            "question": "Is there any information about Boles\u0142aw Wallek-Walewski's family?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6410972476005554,
            "question": "Is there any information about Boles\u0142aw Wallek-Walewski's profession?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.510144829750061,
            "question": "What are some notable people from Lviv?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3368009328842163,
            "question": "Can you tell me about the history of Lviv?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.33020177483558655,
            "question": "What language(s) are spoken in Lviv?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2581818997859955,
            "question": "Are there any famous landmarks or cultural attractions in Lviv?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2231917381286621,
            "question": "What is the climate like in Lviv?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Boles\u0142aw Wallek-Walewski was born in Lviv.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8347_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any famous landmarks or cultural attractions in Lviv?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8347_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What language(s) are spoken in Lviv?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8347_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me about the history of Lviv?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8347_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8347_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8347_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8347_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8347_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8347_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8347_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8347_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8347_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8347_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8347_7.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "The query is \"Boles\u0142aw Wallek-Walewski was born in Lviv.\"\n\nHere's the evaluation:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation:\n\n* The document file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_8347/re-ranker-msmarco/6.txt contains information about Boles\u0142aw Wallek-Walewski's birthdate and place.\n* According to this document, Wallek-Walewski was born in Lviv on January 23, 1885.\n\nTherefore, the statement \"Boles\u0142aw Wallek-Walewski was born in Lviv\" is supported by the provided context information."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents state that Boles\u0142aw Wallek-Walewski, a Polish composer and conductor, was born in Lviv, Ukraine. Therefore, the statement \"Boles\u0142aw Wallek-Walewski was born in Lviv\" is supported by the provided information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}